http://www.theconco.co.uk/privacy-policy/

HomeToiletsRange of ToiletsTipi ToiletsShowersEventsWhy Choose UsTestimonialsLinksContact Us Select PageHomeToiletsRange of ToiletsTipi ToiletsShowersEventsWhy Choose UsTestimonialsLinksContact Us
Privacy PolicyWith the implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) on the 25th May 2018 we have updated our Privacy Policy.This privacy policy sets out how The Convenience Company uses and protects any information that you give The Convenience Company when you use this website.The Convenience Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.The Convenience Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 16th May 2018.What we collectWe collect the following information:Your name.Your contact information including phone number and email address.Your event start date and end date.The type of event, its location, number of guests and post code.What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information so that we can contact you to give you a quote and/or to discuss your Mobile Toilet hire requirements with you.How we use cookiesVisit our Cookie Policy page to read about our use of Cookies.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email info@theconco.co.ukIf you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible at info@theconco.co.uk and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.PoliciesCookie Policy
Privacy Policy
Kniftons Mobile Toilets Limited trading as The Convenience Company is a registered company in England Registered Number 08476984. All Rights Reserved © Copyright 2020 | website services by e4creative
This site uses cookies: Find out more.Okay, thanks
